

Chukwuemeka Maduekwe

Remotely Available Full Stack Developer









Summary

As a Full Stack Developer with a specialization in Frontend Development, I bring a wealth of experience to my role at Zenith Bank. My responsibilities include building and maintaining internal applications. With a background in Computer Science, I hold a degree in the field.

I bring a unique combination of skills, including proficiency in RESTful and GraphQL APIs, web development with Next.js, React, Svelte, and Angular, desktop development using Electron.js, mobile app development with Flutter and React Native, and server-side experience with Express.js and Node.js.

Preferred Tools

- Frontend: Next.js, React, Svelte and Angular
- **Desktop**: Electron.js
- UI: Material-UI, SASS/SCSS, and CSS3
- Backend: Express (Node.js Framework), Mongo DB, and Firebase
- Mobile: Flutter and React Native

Experience

Frontend Developer at Zenith bank April 2021 till date

- Revamped existing applications, at the same time reducing load time.
- Designed and developed new user-friendly app and improved performance.

Full Stack Developer at SoccerMASS Oct 2018 - June 2021

- Fixed bugs in existing websites and enhanced significant improvement
- Oversaw full lifecycle of webapp development for different projects
- Improved search engine optimization for existing and new sites

System Administrator at Nigeria Security Printing and Minting (intern) 2017

- Installation and configuration of software and hardware
- Manage network servers and setting up of accounts and workstations
- Troubleshoot issues, outages and train staff on new technologies
- Ensure security through access controls, backups and firewalls

Education

Abia state University, Uturu

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science (2014 to 2018)